#### Contact

ayushbatwada@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ayush-kumar-batwara-50172417a (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
C (Programming Language)
Web Development

## Languages

Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

### Certifications

Computer Vision - Object Detection with OpenCV and Python

AWS Fundamentals: Going Cloud-Native

Python Programming with Data Science

# Ayush kumar Batwara

UG CSE Student at IIIT Naya Raipur. Software developer,AI Enthusiast, Competitive Programmer

Jaipur Metro Rail Corporation

# Summary

I am currently pursuing BTech(CSE). I have worked on various areas like web development and deep learning. Some of my projects are breast cancer detection, sentimental Analysis, smart irrigation system, Automatic Attendance system, website of online Examination system, website of Training and placement cell. I won 1st prize in web development, performed in college fest "Technovate". I have good grasp on Software development and deep learning areas. Good in programming.

## Experience

Krayonnz (Vedarsy Technologies Pvt. Ltd.) 4 months

Software Engineer
July 2020 - Present (2 months)
Jaipur, Rajasthan, India

Frontend Developer May 2020 - July 2020 (3 months) Jaipur, Rajasthan, India

## Education

IIIT-Naya Raipur
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Royal Academy

12th, Senior Secondary · (2015 - 2016)

Explore Academy 10th, Secondary (2013 - 2014)